Abdulrahman Salah Masoud

Tala - Al Minufiyah +201012895020

abdulrahman.masoud.official@gmail.com

https://www.linkedin.com/in/abdulrahmanmasoudofficial/

https://github.com/AbdulrahmanMasoud

Career Objective

Challenging position in Fullstack Development with a creative work environment to enhance experience in web development and application design. My humble experience with PHP and Laravel Framework so I can work with different things like Rest API and also I can do API Documentation using Swagger – and I can work as a frontend developer without framework

Education

 Egyptian Ministry of Communications -Awarded web development Course

Specialty: Web Development

• Psychical Education - Al Minufiyah University

Degree: Bachelor

Specialty: Practical Training

Grade: Very good

Experience

Google DSC Alazhar/ Back End Developer

Go Mint / Back End Developer(Remotely)

- Responsible to create APIs to use it in frontend

- Do some changes in frontend style

Pear / Web Designer (internship)

- Responsible to learn new things in frontend

- Do some projects with technologies I am learned it

Sept. 2020 -Mar 2021

Sept. 2016 –June 2020

Current Work

Apr. 2020 -Oct 2020

Oct. 2019 -Feb 2020

Projects

- Helpy: helpy is a mobile app that supports the first 3 goals of SDGs, No poverty, zero hunger, and good health.
 I am working on it as a backend developer to create API, this app has a sign in and sign up functionally also has [User Profile] you can update profile data or delete it also has [Marker] you can show-add-update-delete marker and has also [Helped] this to make marker helped done also has [Report] you can show-add-update-delete report on any marker, what technologies I am used it: Laravel, JWT, Swagger check from here
- Like and Dislike System: this a like and dislike system project in this
 project you can make like and dislike on any post,
 what technologies I am used it: Laravel, Livewire Package
 check from here
- Electronic Ecommerce: this electronic ecommerce web site it has a
 dashboard you can see in dashboard admin profile and you can manage
 members in web site and you can add new category and you can add items
 and mange comments, in web site you see index page has some items and
 some details about website also in shop page has items and you can search
 by filters so you can check it to see all details about it
 what technologies I am used it: HTML5,CSS3, JavaScript, JQuery, Bootstrap,
 Owl Carousel, PHP Native, MySQL
 check from here
- Front End Electronic Ecommerce: it is a e electronic ecommerce front end website https://doi.org/10.2007/pnecession.org/https://doi.org/https://doi.org/https:/
- GroupBanner: this project to make images as group banner like: convert
 it to banner and you can download it as image
 what technologies I am used it: HTML5,CSS3, JavaScript, JQuery, Bootstrap,
 PHP Native, MySQL
 check from here

Some Simple Projects:

- open camera on browser using JavaScript check from here
- Google Map API Nots check from here
- PHP Object Oriented Programming Arabic Nots check from here

<u>Skills</u>

Technical Skills: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Bootstrap, JQuery, PHP, OOP, MySQL, Laravel, REST API, GitHub, API Documentation(Swagger), Database Design,

Personal Skills: Searching Skills (I really like do that), Willingness to learn, Practical, Realistic, I really respect deadline, Collaborative

Language: English(good)